(Kim Kang Min plays Choi Si Yeol)
(Park Jin Woo plays Na Aijun)
(Byung Hun as Yeon Joo Ha)
(Kim Hongjun plays Ji Kyusung)
("My idol is chasing me?!")
(2 months ago)
Congratulations to A-One for returning
As far as I know, Si Yeol and Ju Ha are famous friends in the entertainment industry.
right?
Yes, Si Yeol and I met each other from junior high school.
He is my oldest friend
That's right. Before Brother Zhuhe changed his career to become an actor
We practice together every day
We were roommates when we were trainees
We are the closest, right?
Yes, we are the closest
Feelings are the best
That’s why I volunteered to wake Choi Si Yeol up today.
Ah, you said you took responsibility voluntarily?
You guys are back after 3 years. Of course I want to come.
That is to say
Our superstar A-One finally returns after 3 years
Of course I want to listen to the new song
Let's enjoy the new song together
Brother Shi Lie, that variety show I told you about last time
(IMZ Entertainment Ji Hyun Woo’s manager)
can you think about it again
The representative told me to convince you
("Go! Trainee Teacher")
(Visiting students’ classes together
Teachers in the lounge...)
(Hope to play teacher Kim Hyung Joo)
((Reservation person in charge) Na Aijun, Park Tae-hoon, Lee Won-cheol)
Luo Aijun
(Luo Aijun)
-Hey Hyunwoo -Hey Shiyeol hyung
I'm willing to star
Help me convey it to the representative
OK I got it
(Episode 2 Can you like me?)
Although…
I'm about the same age as you
I also know that you, as a variety show rookie,
We should get along well while filming the show.
But let’s leave it to someone with more experience in programming…
I said you are my type
what
Not the image on the show
Teacher Luo Aijun
You are my ideal type
It's been a week since we met
Have you missed me during this time?
He said this...
how should i answer
Today... I have been looking forward to it for a long time
I don't know how to answer him
You seem...
I mean...
You seem to be very idle
Luo Aijun, go to hell
Teacher Luo, it seems that you are the type to speak your mind directly.
No, that's not what I meant
-Wow, it's Choi Si Yeol. - Is it Choi Si Yeol? Everyone, come quickly. - Come quickly.
-Wow -Wow, so handsome.
are we leaving
good
-Good -Finally, as a senior actor with 5 years of experience
-Okay, I got it.
Is there anything you would like to say to people who want to be actors?
Well...I'm still moving towards my dream
-I'll confirm again
-If those who want to be actors can persevere until the end
It will definitely succeed
(Luo Aijun) 4444
what is this
(Luo Aijun) My passbook password
(Luo Aijun) Because I’m about to die
(Luo Aijun) If I die
Help me tell my password to my younger siblings
Help the youngest to pay for college first
The rest will be shared equally by everyone as living expenses
i really love them
I'm going crazy
If you want to confess, please go directly to the person involved.
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work...
drink some water
We're only going to briefly shoot the opening sequence today
So just introduce the whole school easily
OK
Are Shi Yeol's makeup and hair ready?
Wait a minute, I'll confirm
Teacher Luo Aijun
You are my ideal type
Alas, this sentence has been lingering in my mind.
Even if it's just kindness with good intentions
No, you still have to cheer up first.
PD The gymnasium is still under renovation.
Shi Yeol is here
It’s the follow-up song to the second album, a fleeting concept of a gentleman.
At that time, I was heartbroken and regretted because I couldn’t receive the photo card.
thank god
thank you all
Si Yeol is here, ready to start over
Are you leaving?
are you okay
Are your feet okay?
Didn't you just stand there for a long time?
Director Bai called
- It's a meeting about a movie. - I'm not acting.
what
I said I won't act
movie
Haven't you always wanted to act in movies?
why
You have to give me a reason that I can accept, so that I can...
What about you?
Do you have a reason that I can accept?
When you broke up with me
Ji Kuisheng
Do you have an acceptable reason for me?
You have…
New target, right?
Yeah
Then you should have told me earlier
Listen to you with my own ears
Now I can finally accept it
Help me find other agents in the future
Lianzhu River
Zhuhe
On the first floor, go to the bottom and there is the health room.
There's a co-op outside this building.
Do teachers also frequent the cooperative?
Of course
When we don't have class
I will go to the cooperative to buy drinks.
Because I have experienced a long career as a trainee
So I always have a wish
Buy bread or instant noodles with friends at the cooperative
Alas, you like instant noodles so much, but you can only eat salad
how do you know
I'm talking about myself
Don't look at me like this. I'm very strict about drinking.
Then do you want to eat instant noodles with me?
what
Days without drinking restrictions
Let’s go to the cooperative to eat instant noodles together
Teacher Luo
Luo Aijun stop
He said he wanted to eat at the cooperative
Stop, stop imagining
OK... OK
Then go this way
The place you see over there is the annex
Go straight after passing the annex
You will see the back door of the school
The direction we are going now is towards the stadium.
I like it very much
something
It happened to snow. It was very beautiful. I was very happy to see it.
That's it
I like snow very much
Please state the object clearly next time...
what
Because I am a Chinese teacher, I am quite sensitive.
sorry
It doesn't matter
Then let's keep going
It’s usually snowy and cold weather like now
We will all have physical education classes indoors
-So handsome. -Brother is so awesome.
So awesome
I like...playing basketball
Teacher Luo Aijun
are you okay
what
Yes
I'm...ok
can we take a break
card
Because I'm sweating, I'm going to change my clothes.
-Okay -Let's start again after dinner.
Okay, let's have lunch first
Meet back at the gymnasium at 2pm
-Okay, I got it. -Okay -Let's go.
Something big was almost going to happen.
It took a lot of effort to survive
If you continue, your heart won't be able to bear it anymore.
Is it such a blessing to come to school to teach?
Ah, it’s time to grab tickets for A-One’s concert
(Estimating your queue number)
How about Teacher Luo?
did you behave well
Not bad
It's very embarrassing because it's the first time
right
No. Children are also very out of control.
I'm in class and these guys keep looking out the window
I didn't know until this time
A-One? They are such famous idols
Super famous
Didn't they sing that song?
You should all know it when you hear it, right?
But there are five members in the group
No, it's four
出道前是五位
One person left the team due to injury and now there are four
This is it
Isn't it six?
Let’s just say four.
How many are there?
Teacher Luo is very young, you should all know that.
I'm not sure either
Because I don't often watch TV
But he probably won't eat with us, right?
No one was seen
He is an artist
And this is all work for them
I definitely want to finish work early and go home.
I really want to go home
Also, everyone I meet will post it and say they are fans.
They must be very tired
Super
I just can't do it
I'm very envious
Yes, you can still make a lot of money.
That's great
(The number of people in line now is 789362)
630,000…
8769 people
There is a sense of distance immediately
(Four-member boy band A-One makes a successful comeback after three years
It topped all music charts within an hour of its release)
Brother, does it really not matter if you don’t eat anything?
Yeah, it doesn't matter
Why don't you take a break?
Staying by your side like this is just resting.
Let’s talk about the teacher in charge
Teacher Luo Aijun
He's not very good at doing shows.
Are you okay?
if you want to be more comfortable
Do you want them to change to someone else?
No need
No need to change
No need to change?
Yeah
He is very cute
(Mom)
Will be ready in ten minutes
-I'm going back. -Okay, I'll get ready.
-Here you go. -Okay.
Aijun
Yeah mom
I have to go back now
are you in a hurry
Well, there's no urgency
I saw the living expenses you remitted.
not much money
You use it to subsidize the education expenses of your younger brothers and sisters
I'm always grateful to you Aijun
After you become a teacher
People around me are envious of me
You should listen carefully to what your superiors say
Always behave well and don’t be too conspicuous.
You know, my son
Well I know
I sent Xinqi there. You and Kuisheng should remember to eat it.
I know
I'm going to hang up the phone
Mom, I'll call you later
-Okay. You should be very busy. Take good care of yourself. -Yeah.
He is an artist
And this is all work for them
I definitely want to finish work early and go home.
Also, everyone I meet will post it and say they are fans.
They must be very tired
Super
I had unrealistic expectations for a moment
It's simply impossible
For Shi Lie, this is just one of the things he does every day
He just showed me a little kindness
See the reality clearly
This is a hard-won contract job
I can't offend anyone
So I want to be like before
Just watching from a distance...
(Mom)
Oh yes, Zheng Zhu’s mother went to Kota Kinabalu
She said it was nice there
I didn't expect you to come in. I...
Just talking on the phone
You sweat a lot
Are you feeling unwell?
I saw that your expression was not very good during the filming process.
No
Because I came here after dinner
That’s why I sweat
In this weather?
I'm always afraid of heat
Yeah...in this weather
Sure enough, it's because I choose you
Makes you very stressed
Because the first person I saw when I came to Luoguang High School
That’s Teacher Luo Aijun
I do this because I want to get closer to you
can you like me
just a few minutes ago
I just made up my mind here
But what this kid said
Just beat me back to my original shape
I…
Anyone who sees you will think you are handsome and good at doing shows.
And the classmates in our class also like you very much.
That's good
let's go
good
Because it was the first day, I NGed many times
I don’t know if it has caused you any trouble
sorry
You don't need to apologize
It was also my first time, and I was actually very nervous.
Do professionals like you get nervous?
So magical
Is this the first time I’m shooting today?
If we can finish today successfully
Should we help each other realize a wish?
Wish...wish?
Is there nothing you want me to do?
just a few minutes ago
I just made up my mind here
But this kid's expression made me...
The army is defeated
I…
have a wish
"My idol is chasing me?!"
-Thank you for your hard work. -Thank you for your hard work.
Kuisheng
If you suddenly act like this, I will feel very uncomfortable.
wait a moment
Let's meet and talk
I forgot to put stickers inside
I'll do it
-Is it okay? Okay, I understand. -Is it okay?
-Thank you for your hard work. -Thank you for your hard work.
Kuisheng
nice to meet you all
I am Choi Si Yeol, a Chinese language intern teacher.
Shi Yeol’s face that I always see in videos
- You're really well behaved. - Ah, thank you.
Thank you for your hard work
-Thank you for your hard work. -Yeah
That unfamiliar face is so strange
Different atmosphere…
Did something really happen?
No matter what, it's best to maintain the status quo, right?
Please tell me what did I do wrong?
That's right
It’s because of Teacher Luo Aijun
What